<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DemoApp</string>
    <string name="btn_next_label">Next</string>
    <string name="mount_vesuvius">Mount Vesuvius</string>
    <string name="vulcanos_information">Mount Vesuvius (pronunciation: /vᵻˈsuːviəs/; Italian: Monte
        Vesuvio [ˈmonte veˈzuːvjo]; Neapolitan: Vesuvio; Latin: Mons Vesuvius [mõːs wɛˈsʊwɪ.ʊs];
        also Vesevus or Vesaevus in some Roman sources)[1] is a somma-stratovolcano located on the
        Gulf of Naples in Campania, Italy, about 9 km (5.6 mi) east of Naples and a short distance
        from the shore. It is one of several volcanoes which form the Campanian volcanic arc.
        Vesuvius consists of a large cone partially encircled by the steep rim of a summit caldera
        caused by the collapse of an earlier and originally much higher structure. Mount Vesuvius is
        best known for its eruption in AD 79 that led to the burying and destruction of the Roman
        cities of Pompeii and Herculaneum, as well as several other settlements. The eruption
        ejected a cloud of stones, ashes and volcanic gases to a height of 33 km (21 mi), spewing
        molten rock and pulverized pumice at the rate of 6×105 cubic metres (7.8×105 cu yd) per
        second,[2] ultimately releasing a hundred thousand times the thermal energy released by the
        Hiroshima-Nagasaki bombings.[3] More than 1,000 people died in the eruption, but exact
        numbers are unknown. The only surviving eyewitness account of the event consists of two
        letters by Pliny the Younger to the historian Tacitus.[4] Vesuvius has erupted many times
        since and is the only volcano on the European mainland to have erupted within the last
        hundred years. Today, it is regarded as one of the most dangerous volcanoes in the world
        because of the population of 3,000,000 people living nearby and its tendency towards
        violent, explosive eruptions of the Plinian type, making it the most densely populated
        volcanic region in the world.[5]
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_edit">EditActivity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="add_note_title">Add Note</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
</resources>
